Uka's Happy and Fufuna Showdown!
Good evening everyone, we are Uka!
Thank you for your cooperation.
Today's progress will be delivered by
me, Yua Miyazawa.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Riju Murahoshi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Aoi Ruri. Nice to meet you.
Today is the 206th time.
Thank you for watching our showroom.
Thank you.
Now, the original avatar of UCCA will be
given as a gift in this room.
So, please throw a gift and get it.
It seems that it is good to throw even
once.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you.
I hope it will increase more and more.
And, there is also Ruri's avatar.
Yes, there is.
Really?
There is also Rina's avatar.
Yes, there is.
Which one is it?
It's purple.
It's really purple.
It's a round and a rainbow.
It's a kind of ornament.
It's cute.
It's unique.
That's right.
Please get a lot of UCCA icons.
Please.
Now, it's time to spread the news.
Yes.
To make many people watch this show
alone, we will post a post on our
Instagram.
Please spread the news.
Please.
Well, what should we do?
What should we do?
What should we do today?
Today, it's raining.
It's raining, but it's going to be
exciting.
We will go with a wavy hair.
Yes.
Let's go with a wavy hair.
What should we do with the comments?
The comments...
It's great even if it rains.
Let's go with the feeling that it's the
best even if it rains.
Thank you.
Please.
Then, I'll post it when the comments
come.
It's a wavy hair.
It's the same as my image of smiling.
It's wavy hair.
What?
No way.
Is it different?
I don't know.
I think it's a wavy hair.
It's wavy hair.
Oh, this one.
I see.
But it's a wavy hair.
I wonder what it's like.
Oh, this way.
I see.
Oh, here it comes.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Ready, go.
Wow.
It looks like a rainbow is going to
fall.
Rainbow, rainbow.
Are you ready?
I think we are ready.
Please look forward to it.
First, we will start this segment.
We will announce the news in 15 minutes.
We will talk about what happened
recently.
But please be careful with the time.
Of course.
I am not sure.
It's not easy to be careful.
We will talk about it as usual.
Right.
We will talk about what happened in the
group in 15 minutes.
And we will talk about what happened to
the members.
After 15 minutes, the story will be
over.
If you want to see it in 15 minutes, you
can stop at the middle.
I understand.
Let's go.
Let's start.
On April 14th, we went to Osaka.
We appeared on the tour of the girl
group,
which is called,
Thank you.
We covered the song called,
Yes.
It's amazing.
We love to search for things.
Our manager also liked to search for
things.
So we decided to cover this song.
Anyway,
I wanted to do the part where we step on
the first part of the intro.
But at first,
I was like, what?
How do I do this?
I saw it in the video.
I didn't know it.
It was quite difficult.
It was very difficult.
Especially,
If the foot goes over,
I think it's called club step.
I see.
But when going inside and outside,
I have to move it.
There are small steps.
It was very difficult.
How was it, Buri-san?
I was looking forward to the right side.
It was left in the video,
But I was looking forward to the right
side.
I was wondering if I could do it.
I tried hard at the end.
It was difficult.
I couldn't go to the left.
It was hard.
I did my best to kick.
I was on the TikTok of the director.
Please check it out.
How was it, Yu-chan?
I was in the UCCA for the first time, so
I was really looking forward to it.
I think I covered a song by Bashiho
called Oshioi.
It was my first time covering a full
chorus.
I really liked the song.
I watched it on YouTube, so I had a lot
of fun dancing.
It was really fun.
I was really excited to see your
support.
I was really excited.
Thank you.
I hope we can come back again.
Please.
Thank you.
Next.
Can I talk about myself?
Yes, please.
I dyed my hair blue.
Did you notice?
Yes, I noticed.
I didn't have any comments.
I thought so, too.
I noticed your hair.
It's changed a lot.
I've never seen such a bright color.
I didn't notice it.
I noticed it when I came here.
Really?
Did you really notice?
I was commenting.
I'm sorry.
I was looking down at you.
I was a little bit blitzed.
It was a report that it became brighter.
It's amazing.
It's like a gyaru.
I love it.
It's true.
Ruri gyaru.
Ruri gyaru is born.
It's a Ruri gyaru.
It's flying.
I heard it.
It's good.
It's really cute in my mind.
Thank you.
It's difficult.
I'm sorry.
What color?
I don't know.
I noticed it and it became this color.
It's a little greenish.
It's a grayish color.
It looks like this.
It's cute.
It's a gyaru.
Then, I'll go with that flow.
I cut my hair.
It's like a gyaru.
I didn't cut it long.
I'm not sure if you can see it.
I'm wearing a layer.
It's a necklace.
Cute.
It's cute.
I was talking about hair.
I thought I dyed it because it was
flowing.
It's not.
I don't dye my hair with black hair.
I did my hair two months ago.
It was my first time at that time.
I was a little scared and I was a little
nervous.
I thought I wanted to put a little
deeper.
Then, my hair is curled inside.
It looks good.
It's good.
No one noticed about this in the
comments.
I thought I would tell you that I cut my
hair at first.
If you cut it, it's a bit hard.
It's like you're holding my hair inside.
It's not there anymore.
It's strange.
Do you notice it?
It looks good.
Thank you very much.
I tried to put it in.
How was it?
Yuu,
in that flow,
What about you?
I tied it.
I cut my bangs.
I think it's Ruri.
It's a little long.
I cut my bangs
because it was too much.
I cut it myself.
Try it with me.
Try it with the bear behind you.
Yuu's...
It's really cute.
Look forward.
There's a bear in your head.
Look a little lower.
Look.
It's Yuu's birthday.
It's cute.
The bear's ears grew.
There was a bear that grew.
There was.
RYU is the most Yume-chan.
The ears are quite big.
I saw it on the screen and I thought it
was cute.
I noticed it.
Yume-chan's situation.
I've made my solo karaoke debut.
I don't go to karaoke very often.
It's been a long time since I've done
it.
It's been a very long time.
It's been a year.
I went to karaoke with my friends.
When I went to karaoke with my friends,
I sang with them.
I want to sing alone.
I thought.
I don't have the habit of going to
karaoke.
I'm going to go to karaoke alone.
I went to karaoke.
Wow!
I was a little nervous at first, but
surprisingly I was able to do it.
Did you get used to it?
Yes, I got used to it.
That's great. You're an adult.
Isn't it fun to sing karaoke alone?
It's fun. I'm a karaoke fan.
I'm the type who can sing karaoke alone.
That's good.
What did you sing?
What did I sing?
I wonder why I sang.
What about you, idol?
I don't sing much.
I used to be a J-pop fan.
I sang Marigold by Ami-O.
And...
I sang the song of Rokuo Shokushakai and
the song of Yorushika Tadaki.
And for the idol song, I sang the song
of Ebichu and Aino Rental and Jump.
That's good.
It was fun.
I started dog-hunting in that way.
What?
That's not it.
I debuted as a dog.
You debuted as a dog.
I did.
You were a dog.
I wanted to have a dog for a long time.
I persuaded my parents and I met them
this time.
What kind of dog is it?
It's Marupu.
Marupu?
It's a dog and a poodle.
It's so cute.
Please come to see me.
I have a dog and I have a dog.
I have a dog.
You have a dog, right?
Yes.
Ruri-chan is saying,
I love you.
You skip me.
I won't lie to you.
You did what you told me you would.
I scared but then you caught me in the
cat.
I panicked.
I wanted to panic.
Because of the time,
I went back to back place.
A couple of years ago,
I went through abdominal change,
minutes after,
and shut down the house.
I had the discussed stock at that time,
but I thought of没有 profit.
Opened my税.
Before that,
I did training at 2 different places.
Is it going to be theнымegiro Efiko-
chan's BGM?
Hey, 280
I'm looking forward to it.
Did you go for a walk?
I haven't gone for a walk yet.
It's a little early.
It's still a little early.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's really cute when I look at the
pictures.
I'm looking forward to your growth.
I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll go with that flow.
I bought 3DS.
3DS.
I thought I'd like to stream games from
now on.
At first, I thought I'd play on Nintendo
Switch.
Sometimes I look at TikTok.
There were people who played 3DS games.
I wanted to play 3DS.
I used to have it.
I had it about 2 or 3 years ago.
It broke.
I couldn't play it.
I want to stream games these days.
I bought a big 3DS.
I bought a big one.
I recently played Animal Crossing.
Do you have a fan?
I have 3DS.
I have it.
I want to play it.
I haven't played it lately.
I went back and forth with it.
I'm a little busy, but I'll come back.
If you will, I will.
I'm poor at playing.
If you have a brand-new favorite, do you
play it?
Many people answer no to me.
But there is something that warms your
heart.
For example, I will play this game
myself this time.
I will.
emphasizes dough
Number one
Gil
I will bring it.
Pokemon is also coming out.
I love Pokemon.
It may be May.
Please watch it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm confident in you.
I want to do it.
I used to play with Ruri.
I played with the animal of Nintendo
Switch.
Atsumori.
Atsumori?
We played Atsumori.
I want to play with the animal of
Nintendo Switch.
Tobimori.
Let's play Tobimori together.
We played it at the store.
I see.
Let's play it.
I'm happy.
I see.
I'm glad that we can meet.
I haven't seen you guys lately.
I agree.
I'm glad that we can meet.
We have lessons and voice training.
We are practicing for the next
performance.
I see.
What is it?
Do you have any ideas?
We are not enough.
Maybe.
We had a lot of events, so we had a lot
of time to meet.
So it was fun.
I feel a little weird.
Because we can meet every week.
I saw the YouTube video you edited.
Thank you.
I edited it.
It was edited by making a reference
video of the spring tour of the Hopp
Park.
It's uploaded on YouTube.
Please watch it.
Please.
It's so interesting.
I laughed watching it.
I was really funny editing.
Yu, Koha, and Moa.
There are too many.
I was wondering how far I could go.
Stay tuned for more information!
Especially listening to you.
What's the first comment?
I was told to sit still.
The three said aroma.
That's where I'd get to the point when I
filmed a video.
´ wrapping up half a box ´
Was it for me?
I was like, I'm going to the bathroom.
I was like, don't go there.
My point is that when Koharu speaks,
it's all in katakana.
It's like a word.
It's like a mysterious girl.
That's right.
It's very unique.
I think the editing was really
interesting.
Ma-chan is also interesting.
Koharu-chan, don't go anywhere.
That's right.
It's cute.
I think the impression of Ruri's dry
body is also cute.
It's cute.
I think it's interesting.
I think it would be nice to see the back
of the members and the new side of the
members.
I hope you can see it and think that you
want to go to the U-Ka's live.
Please take a look.
Thank you.
That's all.
Is there anyone else?
I wonder.
I read one book.
269 pages.
Amazing.
I recently delivered a book and became a
high school student.
I became a high school student.
Congratulations.
I'm the first girl group member to be on
the showroom.
Yes.
I was in the middle of a recent ad.
Thank you.
15 minutes is a lot.
I didn't expect that.
15 minutes?
Yes.
Let's move on to the next corner.
This is the next corner.
10 rounds of fun.
Yay.
Yes.
It's Golden Week.
Amazing.
This year's Golden Week is 10 rounds.
It's hard to do 10 rounds.
If you have 10 rounds, what kind of
schedule do you have?
I want each member to write it down.
I want each member to introduce it.
I want the listeners to decide on the
schedule.
Who do you want to be on the showroom
with?
We will decide on it.
We will vote for each member.
And then we will decide the order.
I see.
Good.
This time we will decide on each
member's individuality.
Certainly.
I'm looking forward to it.
What will everyone do when you have 10
rounds?
Yes.
What will everyone do?
This?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I'll start drawing from the first day.
What would you do if you were me?
What would I do?
I'm not sure. I'll draw my ideal.
I feel like I'm going to do this in real
life.
If I have a charger.
I'll draw it.
I drew it. Perfect.
I drew it.
What is your favorite TV show?
I watch TV shows that I missed.
I know that.
What is your favorite movie?
I want to go to the drive-thru.
I stay home on the last day.
What is your favorite drink?
I wash the stones.
That's good.
What is your favorite movie?
I watch TV shows that I miss.
Hmm...
I want to watch a movie somewhere.
Oh, movie.
Nice.
I want to do it on the chorus.
That's true.
What should I do?
There are many things I want to do.
Yeah.
Okay.
I haven't seen it yet, but I'm going to
watch it.
It's a cleaning.
I want to make it quite fulfilling.
I agree.
It's pretty.
I'm going to eat something delicious.
I'm going to start muscle training for
the summer festival.
What should I do?
I'm lost.
It's difficult!
I haven't done it yet.
You haven't done it yet?
I'm still thinking.
I'm still on the third day.
I'm on the fourth day.
Everyone is late.
Do you have any other ideas?
I want to make a thick dish.
That's good.
What should I do?
I don't know what to do when I decide on
the order.
I agree.
I'm lost.
What should I do?
I like going to a cafe.
I'll make curry with spices.
I like it.
What is it?
Yu is holding a ball.
What should I do?
Let's write our ideal
Wait wait wait
What should I do?
Should I do it the other way around?
I can't do it at all
Finished
Finished?
Yes
I did it
I didn't do it at all
What should I do for the next 3 days?
What should I do?
I can't do it in 10 days
I know
I got it
What should I do?
I think I can do it.
You can do it.
I have a new plan.
Plan B?
I will talk about it later.
Will you tell me?
Thank you.
I'll announce it.
The rest of the 10 days of Aoi Ruri is
like this.
First of all, I will move from the first
day.
I will come to Hawaii.
I will arrive at the beach at night.
From the next day, I will go to the sea
and drink acai bowl and mango juice for
lunch.
I will travel on the third day.
I will go to the beach.
I will eat hamburgers on the fourth day
and go home.
I heard the word hamburger.
What?
Hamburger.
Hamburger is a katakana.
Oh, it's a katakana.
I said it in a katakana.
On the fifth day, I will go home and
rest.
I want to rest my body and have dinner
with my family at night.
That's about it.
From the next day, I will go to Hawaii.
I will travel again.
I will go to Hokkaido.
Oh, you have a great coordination.
I will go to various places.
When I arrive at the airport, I will eat
sushi and play with the cats at my
grandmother's house.
I will rest slowly on that day.
The next day, I will go out and have a
barbecue.
On the eighth day, I want to go to
Otaru.
I want to go to Otaru and see the sky.
I want to do it.
I will go to Otaru in Otaru and take him
there.
On the ninth day, I want to go out with
my grandmother.
Wherever you go, I want to go out with
On the tenth day, I will eat ramen at
the Chitosekuko hall and go home.
It's a very well-stocked type.
It's very outdoors.
I also like to travel, so I have set a
schedule for traveling for almost four
days.
Let's go together!
It's full of action.
It's a lot.
It's not like we spend time at home.
It's nice.
Let's go with YU.
It's the best plan.
Here's YU's 10th day.
The first day is
I go out at home.
I go out all day
and rest my mind and body.
The second day
I go out to eat
and watch movies.
The third day
I go shopping for clothes and makeup.
The fourth day
I go to the beauty salon.
I want to eat something delicious.
The fifth day
I go out to clean my house.
The sixth, seventh, and eighth days
I was going to Okinawa.
I went to Karuizawa.
I went to a natural place
and went to a digital detox.
I want to rest my mind and body.
The ninth day
I go to a coffee shop.
The tenth day I go to bed.
The plan B is
the same as the first day.
I go to bed.
I spend three days in a dreamland.
I stay at a hotel.
I'm in the dreamland.
The third day
I go to Disney.
The fourth day
I go to the dreamland.
The fifth day
I go to the house.
I go to Karuizawa.
My plan is to get everything done
and go to sleep on the tenth day.
My plan is to get everything done and go
to sleep on the tenth day.
This is my e-bike.
It's realistic.
It's a nice e-bike.
I'm going to clean up the house.
This is my 12-day-old house.
I have a job until the first day.
I'm at home for the first two days.
I'm the type who doesn't go out.
I'm at home.
I play games, edit videos, watch DVDs.
I live a relaxed life.
On the third day, I'm going to my local
friend's dream country.
I haven't seen my friends since junior
high school.
I want to go to my local friend's dream
country.
I'm going to stay at home the next day.
I want to clean up the house.
I want to shop online.
I don't have anything to wear.
I live in Osaka.
I have one thing to ask.
I want to travel to Hirakata or the
acquiring tro picnic.
I haven't been to Osaka, both local and
BU so far.
I don't want to leave.
I stopped traveling which I don't have
many time.
I want to estão Place Hirakata.
I want to stay in Tallama too.
I want to do a memory tour.
I came back and came home.
I'm home, but I'm home.
I want to do more than one day.
I want to do a lot of games.
On the ninth and tenth days,
I want to go to Shizuoka with my family.
I want to go out.
That's good.
When I say this,
I'm sure you'll say,
I'm sure I'll go to all the houses.
I think it's like an Indian style.
I can go to both, but I think it's an
Indian style.
It's a dream.
Three people are here.
Which one?
I'm sure it's a dream.
I choose first blabber
everyone please vote
oh delicious
It's a good plan.
How do you feel?
Rui-chan is the outdoor type.
Do you want to?
I want to go out.
I think so.
Rui-chan is like that.
If you have a day off, do you always go
somewhere?
I want to go somewhere, but I don't know
how many days I'll be off.
If I have a day off, I want to go
somewhere.
Can you say it the day after tomorrow?
I want to go to pre-school, but I don't
know what to do.
I want to go to the school that affects
me.
Is it okay? Please vote.
Ruri is the first, Murahoshi is the
second, and Yuu is the third.
I think Yui is an indoor person.
I'm an indoor person.
I have a lot of things I want to do.
I'm an outdoor person now.
I'm an indoor person.
I can't go shopping to the beauty salon.
If you do your best, you can do it on
the same day.
That's right.
I'm an indoor person.
I'm not going to go shopping every time
I have a plan.
Do you understand?
I'm getting annoyed.
I'm a little annoyed.
I'm annoyed.
Let's count 10 seconds.
Period.
We're done.
The result is?
How is it?
What?
That's amazing.
Why?
First of all, I'll announce the results.
2nd, Riju.
Yu-chan is 35.6% in the same rate.
Amazing!
Ruby-chan is 28.8% in the third place.
Why? Everyone is attractive!
It's okay, it's a bit hard.
Maybe it's because there are many Indian
people.
Everyone is number 2 and 3.
Don't you want to know why?
Let's get some comments.
I want to know why you chose her.
If I could choose, I would choose Guam
or Hawaii.
I want to go there.
It's ideal.
It's not realistic.
But both of you are realistic.
You clean well.
I think you are great.
I have a reason.
I heard that you have a good balance.
I see.
You are a good-looking girl and a good-
looking man.
I have a good balance when I'm off work.
I like the sense of integration.
I see.
I like overseas.
What?
I see.
I'm glad that I have two days off.
I think I have more than four days off.
I think so, too.
I agree.
I like the fact that you like it.
I like overseas only when I go to
concerts.
Amazing.
I see.
I also admire overseas travel.
I can go to places I don't know.
I want to go to overseas.
I want to go to the UK.
I haven't been to the UK yet.
I'm sorry.
I think that's all.
If you have 10 days off, please try to
spend a lot of time with us.
Let's have fun in the UK.
Let's have fun.
Let's go to the next corner.
Yes.
Next is...
Children's Day with Yuka.
Yes.
Children's Day is coming soon.
We will continue to spend the remaining
time until the end.
Yes.
Please ask us anything in the comments.
We will be children.
We will answer your questions.
I can't do it.
Children are adults.
I'm 21.
I will become a child if I tap Yui's
hand.
I will do twinkle magic.
I will do it.
OK.
It's dangerous.
Stop the hint.
Yes.
Are there any more questions?
I don't have any more questions.
I can't answer any more questions.
I got it!
No!
I did it!
Can I eat onion?
Yes!
Onion!
I don't know anymore.
I'm sorry.
I can't read kanji.
I can't read Hiragana.
How old are you?
What?
How old are you? 19 years old.
19 years old?
4 years old.
4 years old? That's cute.
How old are you? 80 years old.
80 years old?
Can you eat vegetables?
I love vegetables.
I love peppers, but I don't like
vegetables.
I hate peppers.
You can eat peppers, but you can't eat
vegetables.
I hate peppers.
You can't eat vegetables.
I don't have any other vegetables.
Do you have a mother or father?
I have a mother.
What are you doing?
I don't play with you.
Don't you play with me?
I don't draw.
Ruri?
Ruri.
I'm sorry.
Ruri is cute.
Please draw Ruri.
What do you want to eat?
Gummy.
Ruri.
You are good at drawing.
You are cute.
Ruri has no hair.
That's true.
Ruri has green cheeks.
Ruri has green hair.
Ruri has bangs.
Ruri has a cute hair.
Ruri has three bangs.
Ruri has more bangs.
Ruri is cute.
You draw me, too.
You are cute.
Ruri.
Yes.
Yu-chan, wait a minute.
Yu-chan, good job!
This is a dango.
It was a donut.
It's a dango.
I'm sorry.
I wrote something.
What do you want to ride?
I want to ride a jet coaster.
Can you ride it?
I'm scared.
I can't ride it because my back hurts.
Really?
When I was 20 years old.
I'm sleeping now.
What?
I was sleeping.
Why are you bullying me?
I'm not bullying you.
I'm not tall enough to ride it.
You're a baby.
I'm 165cm tall when I was 20 years old.
I'm thinking about it.
Really?
It's amazing.
It's nice.
What is the question?
Question?
What is marriage?
Marriage is like this.
I know this song.
Promise?
If you kiss me, I'll kiss you.
What is this?
Marriage is bye-bye.
What is a kiss?
Kiss?
It's cute.
A kiss is cute.
What is it?
Is that so?
You're good at dancing.
Really?
I'm good at dancing.
I want to go to the concert someday.
I want to go.
You can't go, Ruri.
Ruri, you're 19.
19.
19, you can do it.
Please go to the live.
What did you do?
I was sleeping.
What?
It's time.
When did you get that time?
It's hard.
It's the end.
I'll announce it now.
Ta-da.
Ta-da!
The Journey Begin...
Sorry.
The Journey Begin Tour Spring Hop Step
Jump is currently in progress.
Yay!
The next performance will be held at
Fukuoka Beat Station on April 27th,
Saturday.
Please come and visit us.
Tickets are on sale.
The Step Show is about to start soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm rehearsing right now.
I'm going to see a lot of different
things.
I can see this kind of Yuu.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please come and visit us.
Please.
And then...
Next...
Sora will be on the stage.
It's a secret.
Please come and visit us.
Next...
Miyuki Rina will be on the stage.
Tickets are on sale.
Please come and visit us.
Please.
We're on sale.
And...
Tokyo Idol Festival 2024 will be held.
Please come and visit us.
Thank you.
This is the first time for us to perform
as a new generation.
It will be held on August 2nd, Friday
and August 4th, Sunday for three days.
Tickets are on sale from today.
Let's enjoy this summer together.
Let's have fun together.
Yay!
That's what it's like.
Anyway, we're doing a spring tour now.
I hope you'll come and visit us.
We'll be at various parks and have fun.
Please come and visit us.
Thank you.
I'll tell you the ranking now.
Okay.
From the 5th place...
The 5th place is...
Where?
Ta-da!
Miya!
Thank you.
And the 4th place is...
Ta-da!
Doctor Dorori
Thank you.
And the 3rd place is...
Cha-cha.
Ta-da!
Ebi-nago
Thank you.
And the 2nd place is...
Thanks.
Thank you.
And the 1st place is...
This is hard.
Ta-da!
Momopono HIDE!
Thank you!
Next time we will be streaming on May
8th, Wednesday at 7pm.
We will announce the members as soon as
we decide.
To avoid missing the stream, please
click the heart icon and subscribe to
our channel.
Please check our individual streams as
well.
That's it for the showroom of the fun of
UCCA!
That's all for UCCA!
Thank you!